Skúli Arnarsson

Looking for a full time job in web, software or app development

General information

SSN: 280995-2079

Address: Maríubakki 28,109 Reykjavík

Email: skuliarnarsson@gmail.com

Mobile: 858-7111

Personal page: skulia15.github.io GitHub: github.com/skulia15

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/skulipardus



About me

I am a 25 year old student at the University of Reykjavík studying computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design. My interests include everything related to technology, programming, alternative and electronic music, video games, exploring the world and experiencing different cultures. I'm a responsible and an extremely reliable employee. I am quick at learning and mastering new technologies and I like working alongside others in a team. I am most interested in working in web- or app development. I am healthy and don't smoke. I don't have a criminal record. I have a driver's licence and I own a car. I am fully willing to relocate.

Education

Reykjavík University – BSc Computer Science

August 2015 - December 2018, GPA 8.74

BSc in computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design.

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (Exchange student)— BSc Computer Science

January 2017 - June 2017

Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð – Diploma(Stúdentspróf) from gymnasia

August 2011 - May 2015 GPA 8.90

Programming languages

- Javascript
- C#
- Python
- C++
- Java
- C
- SOL
- (HTML5)
- (CSS3)

Tools and technologies

- Vue.is
- React.is
- Xamarin
- Node.is
- **Express**
- ASP.NET
- RESTful web services
- .NET Framework
- Webpack
- Mocha
- Bookshelf.js











Work experience

Advania — Software Specialist

June 2018 -

Contracting work for OR (Reykjavík Energy). Developing a variety of internal and external systems. Most of my focus has been spent on web programming and integration. Technologies include Vue.js, React and .NET.

//Jökulá, Advertising Agency- Internship

January 2018 - June 2018

My final Project for University of Reykjavík. We build a "Full Stack" web service / application from scratch. The web service is meant for in-house use at Jökulá . The web service handles allocation, supervision and record keeping for all of Jökulá's projects. The service is implemented using *Node.js* for back end functionality and the front end is implemented using *Vue.js*.

Straumhvörf – Night guard / Standard employee

June 2017 - January 2018

I worked part-time both as a night guard and as a standard employee. The job involved care for people who suffer from serious mental disorders.

Te & Kaffi — Barista

September 2014 - December 2017

I worked part-time as a barista. The job involved working the register, making coffee- and tea based drinks, washing dishes, cleaning and I prepared and waited food. I did everything needed to keep a coffeehouse up and running.

NFMH, Students association of Menntaskólans við Hamrahlíð – *Member of marketing committee*

January 2014 - May 2015

I was responsible for the acquisition of sponsorships and advertisements in collaboration with various companies to finance the students association.

ISS Iceland— Delivery driver

May 2014 - September 2014

I worked as a delivery driver for a summer. I drove around the capital area and delivered clean laundry to various companies and organizations. I also oversaw orders and maintenance in the warehouse I also did various other work in the laundry room.

ISS Iceland— Cleaner / Custodian

December 2009 - May 2014

I mostly worked with cleaning in a mall. I worked full-time in the summer and over Christmas, but otherwise I worked two days a week.

- Pug
- Less
- Gulp
- Bootstrap
- Gi*
- Agile Methodologies
- Istanbul
- Bash

Languages

Icelandic- Native language

English- Fluent

Spanish, Danish- Working knowledge

French, Italian- Little working knowledge

Grants

Freshmen grant from Reykjavík University - For excellent performance in gymnasia.

Erasmus+ grant - For participating in an Erasmus exchange program in Madrid.







ISS Iceland — Cleaner

May 2013 - August 2013

I worked a summer job in public household services for older people and people with reduced mobility in Gardabær. I managed company vehicle.

Fint slf — Cleaner

December 2009 - May 2014

General cleaning, mopping and waxing floors. I worked part-time with school.

Morgunblaðið — Newspaper carrier

February 2007 - September 2007

I delivered newspapers every day of the week.

References

Gísli Rúnar Sævarsson - Owner at Fínt shf.

Phone: 6649099.

Email: gislirun@gmail.com.

Rakel Róbertsdóttir- Director at Straumhvörf.

Phone: 695-8501.

Jónína Gunnarsdóttir - Service representative at ISS.

Phone: 6964924. Email: jonina@iss.is.









Academic record at Reykjavík University

Course		Date	ECTS	Grade	Rank
T-107-TOLH	Computer Architecture	06.11.2015	6	9,5	30-55/228
T-111-PROG	Programming	06.11.2015	6	9,0	28-48/190
T-114-VERK	Problem Solving	16.11.2015	6	9,0	60-123/251
T-117-STR1	Discrete Mathematics I	19.11.2015	6	8,0	23-36/173
T-113-VLN1	Semester Project 1	31.12.2015	6	8,5	184-221/262
T-216-GHOH	Software Requirements and Design	11.04.2016	6	9,0	13-34/224
T-419-STR2	Discrete Mathematics II	14.04.2016	6	9,0	27-50/153
T-201-GSKI	Data Structures	18.04.2016	6	8,0	63-86/204
T-213-VEFF	Web-Programming	22.04.2016	6	9,0	33-64/242
T-220-VLN2	Semester Project 2	31.05.2016	6	8,0	150-183/230
T-303-HUGB	Software Engineering	09.11.2016	6	8,0	52-92/219
T-301-REIR	Algorithms	15.11.2016	6	9,0	22-40/208
T-202-GAG1	Databases	21.11.2016	6	8,5	40-66/222
T-317-CAST	Calculus and Statistics	24.11.2016	6	9,0	9-17/134
T-308-PRLA	The Python Programming Language	31.12.2016	6	8,5	34-43/99
T-215-STY1	Operating Systems	21.06.2017	6	Transferred	
T-513-CRNU	Cryptography and Computer Security	21.06.2017	6	Transferred	
T-622-ARTI	Artificial Intelligence	21.06.2017	6	Transferred	
T-636-SMAT	Human Computer Interaction	13.11.2017	6	9,0	1-2/19
T-302-HONN	Software Design and Implementation	14.11.2017	6	9,5	3-5/56
T-514-VEFT	Web Services	16.11.2017	6	9,0	12-25/93
T-409-TSAM	Computer Networks	23.11.2017	6	8,0	34-50/172
T-488-MAPP	Mobile App Development	31.12.2017	6	9,0	5-8/40
T-631-SOE2	Software Engineering II - Testing	09.04.2018	6	9,0	10-18/48
T-501-FMAL	Programming Languages	13.04.2018	6	8,0	26-39/183
T-427-WEPO	Web-Programming II	20.04.2018	6	9,5	8-11/88
T-404-LOKA	Final Project	31.05.2018	12	8,5	43-86/129
I-406-IERP	Introduction to ERP Systems	31.12.2018	6	8,0	36-40/48
T-542-HGOP	Introduction to quality management and testing	31.12.2018	6	10,0	1-2/33

ECTS required for BSc in Computer Science - general: 180





Total ECTS:

Average:

180,00

8,74

